Lambayeque, Perú
LinkedIn/jhangmez
https://jhangmez.xvz

Jhan Gómez P.

+51 917463991 <u>Github/jhangmez</u> <u>jhangomez25@gmail.com</u>

I am a student at the end of my degree in systems engineering oriented to web development. I have more than 1.5 years of experience as a frontend programmer, I have used technologies such as React, React native, frameworks such as Next.js and styles mostly with tailwind. I'm passionate about creating user experiences that strike a balance between being easy to use and lightweight without sacrificing too much quality.

Professional experience

Frontend Developer (Project)

Educa Emprendedor

April 2024

On-site

Lambayeque, Peru

- Developed their landing page in accordance with brand alignment, applying best development practices.
- Initialized their backend connection using tRPC.
- Worked closely with the Design team to ensure project coherence and attractiveness.
- Conducted a study to determine the structure and design of the database, including the creation of the entity-relationship diagram as part of my responsibilities in the role.

Freelance Frontend Developer

Freelancer/Independent

Sep 2023 - Present

Remote

Lambayeque, Peru

- Developed landing pages, ensuring high conversion rates and brand alignment.
- Architected and built a fully-functional platform utilizing best practices (e.g., component reusability, state management) for optimal performance and maintainability.
- Contributed effectively in team meetings, actively participating in planning discussions and collaborating on project goals.

React Native Junior Frontend Developer

Bartebi/Agrokasa

May 2023 - Jun 2023

Remote

Lima, Peru

• Built mobile applications using JavaScript and the React Native framework, leveraging libraries like Material UI's Paper for robust and attractive UIs.

React Junior Frontend Developer

Bartebi/Agrokasa

Feb 2023 - May 2023

Remote

Lima, Peru

- Developed dynamic and user-friendly front-end elements using JavaScript and the React framework, incorporating libraries like Material UI for consistent appearance and interactive features.
- Integrated external APIs seamlessly to enhance functionality and data flow within the platform.
- Collaborated effectively in team meetings, contributing to planning sessions and project management.
- Demonstrated punctuality, responsibility, and commitment to deadlines, consistently exceeding expectations and taking ownership of assigned tasks.
- Thrived in a remote work environment, showcasing excellent self-discipline, adaptability, and a strong learning appetite.

Documentation Manager

Agencia Consigue Ventas Online

Dec 2022 - Feb 2023

Remote

Lima, Peru

- Designed, implemented, and managed the documentation for the agency's various departments.
- Led and coordinated the documentation team.
- Advised the agency's departments on documentation matters.

Promoted a culture of documentation management and structuring within the agency.

Documentation Analyst

Agencia Consigue Ventas Online

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022

Remote

Lima, Peru

- Collected, analyzed, and organized the necessary information for documentation.
- Prepared documentation using established formats and standards.
- Updated documentation on a regular basis.
- Provided feedback to users on the documentation used.

Technologies and Languages

Languages: JavaScript, Typescript

• Technologies: ORM Prisma, Postgresql, Graphql, Git, Next.js, Nexus, Expo(React Native), tRPC

• Other: Data Structure, Tailwind, Material UI

Education

Systems engineer student, Universidad Nacional Pedro Ruiz Gallo, Lambayeque, Perú.
 (Sep-2024)

Personal projects and freelance projects

- <u>Educa emprendedor</u>: Initialize the project, this included Next.js frontend, React, Typescript; database with Postgresql and backend with tRPC, you can check the project on <u>their web page</u>.
- <u>Sensors Expo Typescript</u>: This is a simple project that uses the examples of expo sensors with respect to react native, but adapted for typescript, this project will be constantly modified for the future to train a neural network model through the data collected from the sensors. This will be a topic to present before a scientific conference.
- Quatu: This is a project that has been in development since December 2023, powered by next.js typescript with React, nextUI styles along with tailwind. It manages a server with a Graphql API, with which requests are transmitted to the database, this is managed by the Prisma ORM, you can check the changes and progress on the github project.
- Quatu Graphql Server: This is the graphql server powered by Apollo Server, on which all Quatu requests are made.
- <u>Developer portfolio (Other link)</u>: This is my portfolio or CV on the web, it works with next.js typescript with React, nextUI styles along with tailwind, it is being modified to adapt different languages through i18n, you can check the changes and progress on <u>the github project.</u>
- Hanpy: Just a landing page designed by me.
- GamarraStore: Just a landing page design by me, it's still in development. It's a Quatu development.
- Harkaysoft: Just a landing page designed by me. It's still in development.
- Limby: It's my first landing page design by me.
- <u>Datrack</u>: I developed their landing page.

Social

- Github:- My personal github, where I host all my repositories
- <u>Linkedin</u>
- Medium

Other languages of my resume

Spanish